

Personal

- Name Uğur Cengiz
- **Address** İzmir
- **Email** ugurcengiz.mail@icloud.com
- Date of birth 17-08-1994
- Gender Male
- Website ugurcengiz.com
- LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/ugurcengiz

Interests

- Playing Guitar
- Walking in Nature

UĞUR CENGIZ

I'm Fullstack DevOps Developer with 4 years experience. I develop web applications, microservices, API integrations using Laravel, PHP, Vue, React with RDS like mySQL, postgreSQL. I use node.JS for backend as well with Next.js. I always consider learning new things, use them and stay updated. In devolopment process i give importance using Source Control, Tests, CI/CD. Besides all this, I am interested in developing games with Unity Engine.



Work experience

2020 - 2023	Software Developer Tagum, Izmir
	I developed e-invoice creation automation system that works with JSON files which gives handy solution for clients. I developed ERP application and create plugins that connects biggest Marketplace API's and process them to account and create auto generated-einvoices. I developed micro-apps running background on server to check application/service health and recover in case of unexpected situations.
2017 - 2018	Web Developer Bulrog, Izmir
	At the time i improved some Warderson Divaine Wrote vectul tools

At the time i improved some Wordpress Plugins, Wrote useful tools that gets datas in csv files and create queues to send bulk-emails.

2016 - 2017 Web Developer

Calisto, Izmir

I developed CRM projects and improved built-in features.



Education and Qualifications

2024

Computer Programming

Bandirma Community College, Balikesir/Bandirma



Skills

Javascript	****
PHP	****
C#	****
Laravel	****
Linux/Terminal	****
Docker	****
Unity Game Engine	****